statecollege.com 2008-06-28

# State College, PA - Privacy Statement

We at StateCollege.com understand your need to maintain your privacy when using the Internet for your communication, shopping, exploration and entertainment. These are the policies StateCollege.com adheres to in maintaining this site for your use. Please note that websites to which StateCollege.com links may have privacy policies that apply only to that website. Therefore, you should refer to those individual websites for their unique privacy policies.

**PRIVACY POLICIES**

**Policy 1.**  
We will explicitly ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us or one of our merchants to contact you ("Personal Information"). Generally, Personal Information is requested when you register for a site, when you request a particular service or information from us or one of our merchants, when you purchase a product, when you fill out a survey, or when you enter a contest. When possible, we will give you the chance to make sure your Personal Information is correct and up-to-date. We reserve the right to contact you for informational or promotional purposes using Personal Information submitted by you through StateCollege.com, unless otherwise notified by you. You may stop the delivery of informational or promotional mail from us by editing your membership account or following the instructions on the email delivering the information.

**Policy 2.**  
We have important business relationships with certain third party service partners ("Service Partners"). These Service Partners allow us to offer you a broader array of services than we could provide to you on our own and assist us in the operation of our site. Our Service Partners and we use your Personal Information to operate the site and services that we offer, and to inform you of new features, services, and products available to you.

**Policy 3.**  
We may also carefully select other companies to send you information about their products or services which are related to the site's service but are not necessary to its operation ("Other Companies' Use"). If we intend to use your Personal Information for Other Companies' Use, we will provide you with instructions on how to decline this service. You may also stop the delivery of informational or promotional mail from us, or from other companies referred by us, by following the instructions on the email delivering the information.

**Policy 4.**  
We do not believe that any portion of our site directly solicits children 15 years old or younger. However, if we develop a portion of our site that does directly solicit children age 15 years old or younger, we will not directly solicit Personal Information from children, nor provide it for Other Companies' Use without first attempting to obtain the consent of a parent or guardian. If possible, we will also endeavor to provide e-mail notice to parents that their children have provided Personal Information to the site.

**Policy 5.**  
We may disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates; (b) protect and defend our rights or property or those of our users, and (c) act as immediately necessary in order to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

**Policy 6.**  
If at any time you believe that we have violated these Policies, please notify us by e-mail at support@lazerpro.com and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly investigate and remedy the problem.

For more information about our privacy statement, see the following Frequently Asked Questions.
